Kaʻahumanu?
Wait.
Maui has opened her skies.
There it is.
Kapuahi?
Can you tell me the story again?
Again? I shouldn't be teaching you at all.
The Star Map is a study for men only.
Since when have I cared
what is only for men, uncle?
The Red Star,
Kapuahi,
was a warrior of great accomplishment.
With his red cape of fire,
he travels the heavens in search
of the "waters of life".
He finds it every night,
beyond our skies,
and gives it to his love,
so she may rise again every morning,
as the sun in our sky.
Our ancestors followed the Star Map
to find these islands,
but what lands lie beyond our known skies?
None worth leaving here for.
Wood from the ʻUlu tree.
These canoes are from Hawaiʻi's kingdom.
Find Kaʻahumanu.
What's going on?
We will find out soon enough.
Father!
What are you doing here?
You did not send word
that you were coming.
Kahekili has attacked Oʻahu, unprovoked.
War is coming to the islands.
I am here to take you back with me
to Hawaiʻi's Kingdom.
Tonight?
Soon Maui will close its shores.
When that happens,
I will not be able to come here anymore.
Maui and Hawaiʻi are enemies as well.
I am Kahekili's sister.
Hawaiʻi would never welcome us now.
You will be welcome.
I have promised Kaʻahumanu's hand
in marriage to my Chief.
What?
Father,
I would not deny you anything,
but this...
Please,
do not make me do this.
Prepare yourself.
We must leave.
Kaʻahumanu!
Leave her, Moku.
She has earned her pain tonight.
We planned for this day.
Not like this!
We must go now, my Chief.
Go with your men.
I will prepare Kaʻahumanu and send her.
And you?
I am the royal blood of this kingdom.
My place is here.
Take care of our daughter.
Son...
You are troubled.
Oʻahu was not preparing
for war against us.
You lied to bring us here.
This does not feel like prophecy.
I expect many will see it as you do.
We have waited generations
for the Prophesied One to lead us,
but I realized
that he is nothing more than a king
who is willing to sacrifice everything
to bring its fulfillment.
Where other kings have failed,
I will not.
Keep your eyes here.
Don't give them a reason
to wonder what you're thinking.
They know what I'm thinking.
There's no need for this.
We could leave now.
Not with the Boar Men watching over us.
We are familiar with how to gut pig.
Even roast them over hot rocks.
That's enough.
I know what we must do.
Kahekili has ordered me to the temple,
so I will go.
I will alert the King.
Wait outside.
Kaʻiana?
Bring him back.
We have man power and full sails.
Send men to sweep the eight oceans.
There is no need to sail blind, my King.
I know where he is going.
Kaʻiana left Heke to the safety of Maui.
His wife, Kupuohi, will go nowhere
without her sister.
Kaʻiana has taken sail for Maui
on the currents of Kaiwi.
We will catch him,
and bring him back alive.
No.
According to my Seers,
it isn't Kaʻiana's breath we need,
it is the mana he carries in his bones.
Bring them to me.
What is that?
Forward!
The King's men won't be far behind.
Move quick!
Heke!
- Heke!
She's not here.
Kahekili's warriors?
There is no sign of intruders.
We have to hurry.
Find them!
Where is she?
She is not a careless girl,
we will find her.
Here!
Last night was the Akua Moon.
Second of the four fullest.
The night she gives offerings
to the forest gods for their medicine.
Heke is in the valley,
replanting what she harvested.
We will find her at ʻĪao.
He's here!
We must help Kaʻiana.
He will find us.
If we fight, we all die!
Kupuohi is right.
We go.
We find Heke.
We split up.
I will lead men on the path of the river.
Kaʻiana will not die by your hand.
When he is found,
bring him directly to me.
When we find him,
I will tear his flesh with the tusks
of our guardians.
In and out. No attention drawn.
We don't wanna end up like Captain Cook.
Don't fire your weapons unless
absolutely necessary.
We need to fill this
for the rest of our voyage.
So keep your eyes open.
Kaʻahumanu,
I've brought fresh candlenut oil.
I thought you might need it.
I am not to be married today.
No, but,
you go to see the Prophetess,
to prepare for what is to come.
You will soon be the wife of a Chief,
don't go to him as a girl of indecision.
I know this
is not what you saw for yourself,
but it is what you must do.
I see the storm that stirs inside you.
You're asking me to tame it.
No, Kaʻahumanu.
Sometimes the storm is all we have.
Taula?
I am Kaʻahumanu,
daughter to the Chiefess Nāmāhana.
I have come to seek your counsel.
A relative of the King
can find counsel with his Seers.
Why come to me?
I have never lived among the King's court.
They do not govern me.
Then ask what you will.
My father will have me leave
the sands of my birth
to marry a Chief of Hawaiʻi.
Do you see any happiness for me?
Because I see nothing but misery ahead.
You will disappoint both your father
and Chief.
You will not bear your Chief an heir.
Then all is lost for me.
Many paths lead to misery for you,
but there is one that leads to freedom.
How can I find it?
You cannot find it alone.
A guardian will come.
I sense a deep fear.
In me?
My family?
In the gods.
What could the gods fear?
You.
You will break this world.
We feared Kahekili's warriors had you.
Why would Kahekili's warriors...?
Something happened on Oʻahu.
Where is Kaʻiana?
Find him!
Are you alright?
Leave me.
You're hurt.
I am hunted by the King's men.
They will kill you if you help me.
Go.
I do not want your blood on my hands.
And I will not have yours on mine.
I can take you where they won't find you.
Can you walk?
Rest here.
We are still searching.
Kaʻiana mocks us.
The best of Maui's men cannot find
an injured man.
He is fighting for his life.
We will find him.
Every minute he's on my island
feels like a rat crawling in my house.
I must go.
Wait.
You are not ready.
Why would the King's men hunt you?
You bear the family crest of the shark.
A guardian of Maui's greatest Chiefs.
Who are you?
I am no one.
But you know of lineage tattoos
and great Chiefs.
My mother is a High Chiefess,
sister of King Kahekili.
I know the royals of the court,
but I've never seen you.
I share blood with Kahekili,
but he is no family to me.
I was born in a cave, much like this one.
Hidden to escape the King's anger.
About what?
My father.
He is a chief of Hawaiʻi's kingdom
and an enemy of Maui.
I have lived my whole life
in fear of King Kahekili.
Seems we have suffered the same.
I served Kahekili as his War Chief.
But I can't serve him anymore.
A War Chief who runs from war.
You are a chief of contradictions.
Since you and I both suffer
the influence of Kahekili,
perhaps I should know your name.
Kaʻiana a ʻAhuʻula.
Kaʻiana...
I am Kaʻahumanu.
Kaʻahumanu.
Can you move?
If you are found by the King's men
you will need your senses.
It would be wise to wait a little longer.
My father was there
when Cook and the Paleskin came.
I was a child but I remember
the fear in his eyes when he talked
about the power of their weapons.
The Paleskins were defeated easily.
You do not worry more will return?
My worries lie here.
My family waits for me at ʻĪao.
I must get to them
before Kahekili's men find them.
Where will you go after?
I have a canoe waiting
to take me to my father.
Your family can find refuge
in Hawaiʻi's kingdom with me.
There's a new life waiting for me there.
Perhaps it waits for you too.
Don't get the rotten ones, boys.
We need to get fresh fruit.
Remember, this is the stock.
Alright, pick up as many as you can.
Come on, boys. Bring your bags.
Captain.
The Paleskins have returned.
Marley. What are you doing?
Marley, put the musket down.
These men are suffering.
They're here for food and nourishment.
Then why is the rat-face man
pointing a stick at us?
Marley...
No!
You may just have brought
the whole island down on top of us.
This way!
We mean you no harm. Alright?
They will be upon us soon.
It's John's pistol.
We're getting off this island.
What are you doing?
Find my family,
and take them to the safety of Hawaiʻi.
You are going alone?
Your family will not leave without you.
Give this to Kupuohi.
Kupuohi.
I will draw them away.
Go.
Quickly!
We can't wait any longer.
Kaʻiana knows the woods.
He's not the only one who could find us.
You stay, I'm going to find him.
Nāhi wait.
We will find him.
We just need to wait a little longer.
A wife waits.
A brother fights to bring him home.
Nāmake!
Nāhi!
Stop Nāhi!
Enough!
Kupuohi?
Wait.
Lost...
I'm lost.
My crew...
We do not know this man.
He should return to his people.
The Paleskins have returned,
Kahekili's men saw them too.
They could track him to us.
We must go.
Come.
Ready to launch!
Forward!
This is a fitting death for a traitor.
Find the body.
We make sail for Oʻahu.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Settle down, settle down, settle down.
There!
Maui!
It's alright, lad.
Alright. You're safe with us.
We're not turning back. Alright.
We got furs in the cargo, we got...
We got winds to push to the open sea.
You'd be dead if we didn't help,
so consider it a favor returned.