- Thank you.
- Madam Secretary.
- Good morning.
I've devoted my career
to reducing casualties
and improving mental health
in the armed services.
But while we're achieving
success with our conventional
forces, the physical
and psychological burden
is falling
on the Spec Ops community
to a degree that feels...
unsustainable.
Much as we'd like
our elite warriors
to be machines, they are not.
We are going to overhaul
our budget request
before it goes
to appropriations.
Uh, overhaul in what capacity?
Significant reductions
in lifetime deployments
for our special operators.
- So, recalculating allowances?
- No.
I'm talking hard caps.
Mandatory retirements.
We can't keep riding them
till there's nothing left.
We'll be facing a significant
degradation in readiness.
- And the financial implication...
- We'll find acceptable levels.
We've been working
on the budget since June, ma'am.
You're suggesting we restructure
in a matter of days?
All right. Call home,
let your families know
they're running solo
the next few nights.
These operators give their
whole lives to fight for us.
We can give up a weekend
to fight for them.
Let's go.
This is about James Reece,
isn't it?
He's one data point.
Yeah, so, if we don't get
this done in the next 12 hours,
BuzzFeed is gonna beat us to it,
and it's gonna be
fucking embarrassing.
I'm sorry, guys. I have
another meeting, but thank you.
Get to it. Good job.
Thank you, okay?
How could they miss this?
I spoke with
a Dr. Russell in Incirlik.
Apparently he pressed
for more testing,
but Reece
checked himself out A.M.A.
Said he had to be back
for the funerals.
- Wait, so no one in the Navy has seen this.
- Yeah, they got
this guy running around,
leading a platoon,
and his medicals are optional?
That's absolute negligence.
Okay.
So what now?
Well, Reece wants to meet.
I want to know why.
Either way,
I'll have something set
to drop later this evening.
All right.
Are you being safe on this?
I was on the ground
in Sirte when they came
for Gaddhafi.
I think I got this.
Maybe I come with you.
And we never see
or hear from Reece again?
No.
He trusts me.
I need that seat.
All right, Reece,
why did you want to meet?
Have you ever heard
of Saul Agnon?
Or a company called
Capstone Industries?
Hi, guys.
May I take your order?
Uh, yeah.
I'll have the little gems
and the striped bass.
- Of course.
- Nothing for me, thank you.
He'll have the bucatini.
Of course, right away.
Capstone Industries?
Kind of place that only has
a logo on their website.
Agnon, he's the VP
of Asset Management.
I did a little research
of my own, and all their market
investments,
it's, it's, it's fluff.
It's Carnival Cruise Lines,
Planet Fitness, H&M...
Wait, so now the backers of
Planet Fitness are involved?
Just listen.
The point being,
they have an investment pool
of $60 billion.
That's way more than can be
accounted for in public holding.
Well, where do
they have the remainder?
That's what we need to find out.
What about the Iranians?
It was never about Kahani.
He was, he was top-shelf bait.
This...
it's something domestic.
Something corporate.
And it's not over.
This lead on Capstone,
where did it come from?
- Not important.
- It's important, actually.
If I'm gonna run with
information, I need to know
that I can trust the source.
I'm the source.
There's something
I need to show you.
Um... I pulled this
from the Engram Clinic.
I didn't want to show it to you
until I had some context.
It's a tumor, Reece.
It's, um,
about the size of a walnut.
It's on the node between
the hippocampus
and the amygdala.
I spoke with a neurologist,
and she said
that symptoms would
include headaches...
...paranoia, memory confusion.
That's not me.
It's time-stamped
to your arrival at the clinic.
Did NCIS give this to you?
No. Holder never mentioned it.
Right now, I'm pretty sure that
we're the only ones who know.
The neurologist recommended
biopsy.
Without that, there's no way
to accurately diagnose.
And, um, we both know
that you've
been having
confabulatory episodes.
That's not something
that you could explain
with, uh, Jahan Kahani
or with Capstone.
Look in the mirror behind you.
There's a man,
brown cap, wrap-around shades.
- You see him?
- No.
There's just some people
finishing their lunch.
We got to go. Now.
Wait, Reece! Hey.
You have to...
Reece! Reece, wait!
Did you bring your smart phone?
No. Just the burner.
What's going on?
They have eyes in the sky.
- You mean like a drone?
- The man that I just saw is an operator.
Now, he's either here for me...
or for you.
Reece, there's nobody there.
You're imagining things.
I ran an SDR to get here.
The only way they could've
tracked me is with UAV.
Hold.
This is my ride. Get in.
Get in!
Buckle up.
I'm sorry, we're running away
because you think
you saw a guy
in wrap-around shades?
We're not running.
Hold on.
Stay here.
You okay, buddy?
I didn't see you there.
Read that.
Open it!
That's a professional
target package.
Still think I'm losing my mind?
- We need to tell the police what happened.
- No cops.
Reece, that guy came
at you in broad daylight.
NCIS is compromised.
Maybe elements in PD,
we can't be sure.
Right now,
we need to get off the grid.
You know how
to use one of these?
Yeah.
Can't be sure
if you're a known quantity.
You need to lay low
until this thing blows over.
Do you have a place to go?
- Do you?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry I got you into this.
You won't see me again.
Reece.
Give me what you have
on Capstone.
If there's a connection to
you and your men, I'll find it.
You know how to reach me.
All clear!
Crash it!
On me!
On you.
All clear!
Clear!
- Blue! Blue! Blue!
- Blue! Blue!
Going in!
All clear, last room.
- What the fuck was that, Hargrove?
- Sir?
You were on the door.
You should have taken the room.
I'm not paying you
to jerk me off, okay?
I need verisimilitude.
You understand?
Pull that shit again,
you're fucking gone.
Combined accuracy was
83rd percentile.
Speed, 71st.
Not your best run,
but competitive.
Certainly wouldn't want
to be an enemy combatant.
Anyway, my reactions
are still for shit.
You want to run it again, sir?
Uh, wish I could.
No. Lunch break's over.
Come on, let's go.
Steve.
- 2:00 p.m. with Janet Lansing.
- Steve...
2:45, al Khalif.
3:30, the Rexeon board.
4:30, Suri Ratanavanh.
- Ratanavanh? Kill that. One minute.
- Steve?
- Call Gary Mathis...
- We need to talk.
I said wait, Saul.
Tell him we're divesting.
If they need someone to scream
at, they can find a wall.
Send him in.
You're supposed
to be in Santa Barbara.
We have a situation.
Is it that you're not
in Santa Barbara?
What sort of situation?
The kind you don't say
out loud for fear
of someday hearing it played
back to you in a courtroom.
Well, we're secure here.
Gordo's dead.
Reece isn't.
- I'll deal with that.
- This was supposed to be
done in Syria.
Now we got this psychopath
running around California.
He's not a psychopath.
He's a SEAL Commander.
Have some respect.
This is bad, Steve.
If Reece is out there,
and Holder's a breach...
Holder didn't know
anything actionable.
He knew me. I'm actionable.
So speak to Hargrove.
He'll set you up
with a detail for the trip.
I'm not going
to Santa Barbara, man.
Mike Tedesco can sell
his own goddamn company.
Mike's not a salesman.
He has aspirations.
Look, it's time
to focus now, Saul, okay?
The Plano deal has to make.
It has to.
Capstone has sunk
too much money into Nubellum.
The time to sell is right now.
I'm sick of waiting
for Elias Ryberg
to grow some nuts,
and I need you there.
Okay?
You're my closer.
Kurt, send Janet in.
- Oh.
- You should come to bed.
I can't. I have homework.
Hmm.
WARCOM's got you...
jumping over bonfires now?
That's a Zoroastrian
new year celebration, Newroz.
Well, I can see how that's
operationally relevant.
They got us tagged
to the Syrian Defense Force.
Got to learn a thing or two
about Kurdistan.
She's kicking.
Is she?
Wait a minute.
Oh...
- Daddy's little ass-kicker.
- No.
She gets her ass-kicking
from her mama.
You know if you get stuck
out there, I'll be okay.
My mom and dad will
come down and help.
If I do make it back,
then I'll probably
just go fishing, I guess.
Even if I have
to liberate a bird...
and fly myself home,
I'm gonna be here.
I'll be holding
your hand the whole way.
Well, I guess then I'll be
the only girl with a doula
coming straight from the sandbox.
Oh...
Is she going to be okay, Daddy?
Yeah. Yeah, she's fine.
She's just, she's stunned.
She's gonna, she's gonna
fly back to her family.
Coming at you.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah.
Oh, I see you've sprung
for the honeymoon suite.
Mm. All right. You were right.
NCIS put a BOLO out last night.
So, if I were you,
I wouldn't go home anytime soon.
Oh, and that, uh,
your shooter in L.A.?
Locals ID'd him
as Adrian Gordon is.
Former MARSOC, or Raiders,
or whatever the fuck
they're calling themselves now.
Went private
with Talos Tactical.
I haven't dealt with them
directly, but I think it's safe
to say they don't operate
with a moral fucking compass.
Jesus fuck.
Like, just take a breath.
I don't think the burrito's
going anywhere, brother.
I didn't get my bucatini, man.
I don't know what that means.
It means thank you
for this burrito.
- You're welcome.
- Thank you.
Luce.
She had some skills, huh?
Yeah. She could sing, too.
And hold a barre chord.
Yeah, she was
something, brother.
You know, for the life of me,
I can't remember the day
she drew this picture.
Bro, I don't remember
last Sunday.
It was the morning
before Syria, I think.
And, uh...
there was a bird.
A starling, maybe?
Cracked into the window,
killed itself.
- Sounds like your memory's spot on.
- Mmm.
It's there, but only half there.
The other parts...
it's fucking... it's muddled.
Mixed with other memories,
it's like...
like looking
through a kaleidoscope.
Well, you did
get fucking rocked.
I mean, you still getting
those headaches, huh?
No.
- Did you see the target package?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
I mean...
looks like a complete asshole.
You see his little fucking dog?
I mean, what I'm saying is,
I don't really get
a mastermind vibe with this guy.
Yeah. I didn't think so, either.
I'm also gonna take
a dive into Capstone.
We could, but I do already
have someone working on it.
There's a journalist.
And she can help me
do some research
without raising suspicion.
- Journal?
- Yeah.
Hmm. That's good to know.
She know you're here?
- No.
- She know I'm here?
- Of course not.
- You do know you're not the only one on the line, right?
That I am fucking CIA,
and if it gets out that
- you're trying to fucking wage your own war...
- I understand.
- ...in the streets of L.A...
- I'm telling you,
you're clean. I promise you.
You're good. She's an asset.
I know what category
to put her in.
And there's never been
an obligation.
- If you need to walk, I get it.
- Fuck you, I'm not walking.
This isn't an obligation
for me, brother.
I just need to know
we have each other's backs.
- That's it.
- Always.
All right.
There's obviously a bunch
of fucking people
tracking you right now,
so just lay low, please.
- That's what I'm talking about, all right.
- I'm chilling.
And if I find something,
I'll buzz you.
Copy. Ben?
You're not going
to the golf tournament
dressed like Big Lebowski,
are you?
I fucking hate golf.
You're gonna miss.
He's gonna miss.
Look at him, he buys this fancy
Scotty Cameron prototype,
thinks it's gonna fix his game.
The man's a genius, you know,
but I keep telling him,
you can't buy feel.
How was your flight over? Did
they treat you right up there?
Did you get friendly
with a minxy little stewardess?
I doubt Elias flew 13 hours
to talk about
sexually harassing
flight attendants.
I'm not talking
about harassment.
I am talking about
the natural magnetism
of having God-money.
Mr. Agnon.
Always good for a laugh.
I'm not kidding.
Plano is one of, what?
Maybe four outfits on Earth
positioned to buy
Mike's company.
We'll make you a hell of a deal
on Nubellum.
Capstone Industries?
- You're on deck.
- Hey, excellent.
Uh, do we know
who we're paired with yet?
I asked for Bryson DeChambeau.
You are with Steve Davey.
Who the fuck is that?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Come here, let me explain
something to you.
And now teeing off
for Capstone Industries
is Bryson DeChambeau.
I'm not ashamed
to admit we considered
very seriously
an offer six years ago.
I had no idea.
Your work has always
been very impressive.
I really appreciate that.
Before Capstone took us
into military contracts,
I had a different plan
for Nubellum.
And if this sale goes through,
maybe we can explore
that original concept.
There he goes! Getting excited.
The thing about visionaries...
they see an endless
spectrum of possibilities.
Our job as partners, as patrons,
has been to narrow
that band just a bit.
Once Capstone came on board,
once Steve started steering
the ship, well,
that's why we're here, isn't it?
Hmm.
I do prefer your current
orientation, Mr. Tedesco.
Uh, of course. Right.
That mean Plano's ready
to counter?
Mr. Agnon,
I appreciate your perseverance,
but this was by design...
a social visit.
Social. Mm-hmm. Okay.
How about this?
I rented a house off the 16th.
How about I drum up
a little soirée tonight?
Call some friends, some girls.
I got a bottle of Bas-Armagnac
that'll knock you flat.
Then I'll throw
some fresh numbers at you.
If I'm in the ballpark, great.
If not,
we'll always have Bryson.
Hmm.
This... house,
you said, uh, it is where?
Yeah.
Yeah, I got eyes on.
Easy day, brother.
Easy day.
Yeah.
Excuse me, guys.
- Hello?
- Hey, Jord, it's me.
Katie. Shit.
I've been calling you.
What happened yesterday?
Yeah, sorry.
You know, I lost my phone.
Hey, are you okay?
Uh, listen.
I was wrong on the Reece story.
I was all wrong.
What do you mean "all wrong"?
Um...
you know, I think I got
to get out of town for a bit.
I'm... I'm just
kind of burnt out, you know?
No. No, I don't know.
W-What are you talking about?
You're doing this, aren't you?
You're fucking bailing
on me, right?
Sorry, Jord.
- You've been good to me.
- Goddammit, Katie.
So this is what I get
for trusting you, for...
So...
how are we faring in here?
This is good work.
We'll get there.
Mm.
I didn't hire you to pussyfoot.
This is going to get us down
to '05 levels.
That's right.
Some would say it's unwise
to unilaterally
stand down resources.
Would you say it's unwise?
Lorraine,
you have four months left,
and frankly, this might not
make it past committee.
You really want
to end on a loss?
Then we'll whip the votes.
It's a win for at least
half the chamber.
What about our contractors?
Think they'll see it as a win?
Well, if you're
trying to convince me
to feel sorry
for special interests...
They have power.
Which means they have a say.
And your legacy is fully intact
without creating headwinds.
Right.
This is my legacy.
Leaving things better
than when I found them.
Yeah.
Something's happening out here.
Thought you'd want to know.
Hey, sweetheart.
I'm Raven.
- You want some company?
- Hi, Raven.
I do, in fact.
You know, I saw you walk in.
My girl Sasha wanted
to come over here and...
I said, "No, no. He's all mine."
- You said that, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
What do you say we, um...
go in the back
and have a drink in private?
Why don't we sit here and talk?
Oh, I love to talk.
What are we talking about?
I'm looking to party.
Think you could help me out?
You a cop?
Hmm.
No.
You know you have
to tell me if you are.
I'm not sure that's true.
But I'm not.
I can hook you up.
What exactly
are you looking for?
- I've been having headaches.
- Oh, yeah?
How bad?
Real bad.
Well, the DJ's got
some methadone wafers.
Think that'll do the trick?
I think that'd do the trick.
It's $100 each.
And it's a really
good price for you.
Just for me?
Thank you, baby.
Sit tight.
Come on, boss,
what're you doing?
- Come on, boss.
- Let's go, man!
Let's go, get over here, Reece!
Hey, baby.
Everything okay?
I'm just remembering.
Well, this...
will help you forget.
Got to say, you never did
like this kind
of work downrange.
Downrange, we had rules.
Yeah, too many.
It was never
the same after you left.
Hell, I-I thought
about walking, too.
You and the teams,
you're like flowers
and fucking dirt, brother.
You weren't going anywhere, and
you certainly didn't need me.
I'm not sure that's true,
all things considered.
Hey...
let me take this.
What?
I'm gonna let
you have all the fun?
Well, someone's gonna
have a hell of a night.
- Here you go, ladies.
- Thank you.
No, no, no, no, no.
I am telling you,
it is the best sushi
you have ever had in your life.
Don't be ridiculous, please.
It's a fucking revelation
is what it is.
You want to talk about the best?
Have you been
to Sukiyabashi Jiro?
Oh, give me a break with Jiro!
He's fine.
He... he's good, whatever.
But Steve found
this guy, Ta is hi.
We shipped this little guy
over from Hokkaido.
I'm telling you,
this fucking guy speaks fish.
He goes down to the pier,
he starts,
like, whispering
to the-the mackerels
and the skipjack, and I
don't know what they say back,
but it must mean, "Pick me,
I'm fucking delicious."
Sounds like something
I'll have to try.
Great. I'll make reservations.
When?
I don't have a time line.
I must speak to my board.
Fuck your board.
I'm asking you.
Saul, don't.
It's late.
And as much as I've
enjoyed myself, I...
have a flight in the morning.
Elias, we've been
dancing for months.
You want to golf?
We're golfing.
You want to eat fish?
Irasshaimase.
But we've reached the point,
my friend,
where I must compel you
to either
shit or get off the pot.
Does Plano want Nubellum or not?
I'll call our acquisitions team.
Tell Mr. Horn
that I'll have a proposition
by morning.
Good night.
That was out of line.
A man
like Elias Ryberg should be
treated with respect,
not disdain.
Do you have
the slightest concept
how much money I just made you?
Jesus Christ, Mike.
You should be
fucking thanking me.
All right, all of you.
Can I have your attention,
please?
Everybody...
fuck off.
I mean it, you're done. Go home.
Everybody, you're done. Go.
Seriously?
Yes.
We made a lot
of money today, buddy.
We made a lot of money today,
buddy.
Who's my baby?
Ah...
There he is.
- I'll tell you, that thing with the bag, Saul.
- Please...
- Please!
- Listen.
Hey, that thing
with the bag, that was,
that was unpleasant
for both of us. Okay?
Help! Help me!
Help me! Somebody, please!
Help! Help...
Help! Somebody!
Help me...
Help...
You done?
Why does Capstone Industries
want me dead?
I-I...
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Okay, don't fucking lie to me.
I'm not lying, I swear
on my mother's fucking grave!
Does it have something
to do with the tumor?
What?
The tumor in my head, Saul.
You have a fucking brain tumor?
Goddamn it.
Un-fucking-tie me.
I didn't do anything.
You know, I've seen men
withstand horrible things, Saul.
Pain.
Degradation.
The likes of which
you can't possibly imagine.
And they kept their mouth shut.
Because those men
believed in something.
They had a purpose
greater than themselves.
A cause that they'd sooner die
screaming for than to sell out.
That's not you though,
is it, Saul?
You're not a true believer.
You're just... you're a guy
who stumbled ass-backwards
into a world
that he does not understand.
You do not want to die
for this, Saul.
So tell me.
He does...
He doesn't...
he doesn't tell me anything.
- Who?
- It's data isolation.
Compartmentation.
Same as you guys.
- He gets off on that shit.
- Who gets off on that shit?
Steve.
Horn.
Steve Horn. There you go.
Get you a little sip.
Go on.
- Steve's a visionary.
- He, uh...
...he made this fortune
in tech and then
he-he moved over into VC.
He, uh, understands people,
markets, war.
I-I'm just an appendage.
A go-between. I resolve things.
How does Steve execute
an ambush in Syria?
Steve has friends everywhere.
Perks of being a billionaire.
- What was his objective?
- Look, that's...
that's not my department,
but, um...
it's all
about something called, uh...
...Project RD-4895.
- What's that?
- RD-4895.
But I'm telling you,
I don't know what it is.
I-I-I just know
that it's worth a...
a lot of money.
That's not good enough.
No! Come on! Come on!
Listen, man,
I'm telling you, man!
I don't know anything!
I'm just a guy!
You said it yourself!
I'm just a fucking guy!
All right.
All right, I believe you.
Steve Horn calls the shots
and you are
- his little errand bitch.
- Yes!
- Right.
- Yes! That's it.
You don't make decisions.
You didn't want any of this
to happen.
I swear to Christ.
Who did you send
to kill my family?
Hmm?
Have a little more.
I want to go home, man.
I asked you a question.
There's a...
There's a lawyer
out of Jackson Hole.
Marcus Boykin.
He deals in black market
crude all over the globe,
including Mexico.
Mexico?
Boykin hired sicarios.
The trigger man.
The one who got away.
Where do I find him?
Fucking Mexico,
I just said that.
- Be specific.
- "What's the address of the sicario?"
That's not
a fucking question you ask.
- Does Boykin know?
- Boykin doesn't know shit.
He knows routing numbers for...
...incompetent fucking hit men.
He's more useless than me.
You know, downrange
we like to say
that what we do is for freedom.
But what it really is, Saul...
There's evil...
in this world.
It's our job
to look it in the eye,
'cause most folks
don't have the balls.
That's the job. We do it.
All you got to do
is pay your taxes
and stay out of our way,
but you...
Saul...
Steve Horn,
Capstone Industries...
...oh, you wanted
in on the fray.
Now...
you're on the battlefield.
This is a methadone cocktail,
Saul.
You get a quiet death.
And you're lucky.
It's more than you deserve.
Shh.
We were looking
at a place in Tahoe.
I tell you that?
A little cabin
on the west shore.
Lauren had this plan.
She was gonna train
athletes at altitude.
Lucy wanted to live somewhere
she could see all the stars.
That's it.
That's all they wanted.
Dead...
they get nothing.
They get darkness.
In service
of some corporate project.
That's why my wife
and daughter had to die.
This is what I don't get.
Why did they have to bring
the girls into this?
An assassination would
make waves.
If a combat veteran goes nuts,
kills his family,
kills the doctors,
kills himself,
people don't blink.
They needed it
to be more digestible.
Steve Horn,
he's in San Francisco.
Head of the snake.
He can get me
the truth on RD-4895.
But Boykin?
That's our path
to the trigger man.
The one
who killed Lauren and Lucy.
All right.
Answers or blood.
Shooter's choice.
Blood.